Thank you for watching!
Nogisaka no ojimyu
Dong!
Here we go, Bananaman of the Nogisaka City Council, thank you very much for your cooperation!
And then Nogisaka jumps!
Oh, he's finally gone... has he decided he doesn't want to do it anymore?
Is it just one person?
You're the only one who's willing to do it.
who's this?
I'm Suzuki Masayuki.
Masayuki Suzuki, Shibata.
Shibata?
I don't know.
The year-end party's over.
What are you doing?
What are you going to do, Mr. Himura?
Nogizaka sunglasses player
Yay!
We are finally able to send you this project in full swing, right, Shibata?
Yes, I'm very happy.
The words of wisdom from Shibata, who has recently taken on the role of Nogizaka's sunglasses character, are
He does it without any hesitation.
Thanks to the sunglasses...
I see.
I can do anything.
Thanks to the sunglasses
That's why
Tonight, all the members will wear sunglasses and remove the limiter
and challenge various competitions.
The MVP who performs the best will receive a gorgeous prize!
What do you mean, "Sunglasses Championship"?
I'm not ashamed of it.
I'm not embarrassed at all.
Can you take a picture for me?
I'm a little...
I'm embarrassed.
You're embarrassed. You're embarrassed.
Shibata's been here... all day today.
Management, right?
He's the manager.
He comments on various things.
Let's get started.
Let's start with the first project.
Sunglasses Karaoke
First of all, we're going to divide into teams.
Each team will be divided into teams.
Each team will be divided into teams and each team will be a famous sunglass artist.
They will appear on stage singing their representative songs.
and compete with each other in the karaoke score.
Scores will be given.
But if you say, "I liked that performance.
I said, "That was a great performance.
you can add points to the score.
Here's the link.
Okay, let's get started.
Let's start with this team of artists.
Here we go.
Hello!
I don't know who that is.
Who is it?
Kaneka наб de tenha.
You're not moving a muscle because you're wearing sunglasses.
I think I made a mistake.
Thank you for watching.
Oh, that's what I meant.
So, now that we've got that out of the way...
We are Yosui Inoue's team.
Yamashita, how do you like it? Aren't you embarrassed to wear sunglasses?
You're invincible.
Invincible.
But this team is strong even without sunglasses.
They're not shy to do anything.
You don't know much about Yosui Inoue, do you? You don't know much about Yosui Inoue originally.
He's a bit fragile, like this.
How are you?
Here we go!
You don't look like him at all.
But you can do it.
I can't take off my sunglasses.
You're right.
Why do you take them off so easily?
Why do you make it look so erotic?
They don't show us much.
How about an extra point?
I don't know.
It means you made a mistake.
I didn't expect you to be so strict.
Well then...
Two points.
I know it's low, but I gave them two points out of ten.
And now for the next team.
This way, please.
They're here.
Who is it?
Seriously, who is it?
Yumiki?
Yumiki.
I play guitar.
So one day, Sakurai's team...
Thank you very much.
The henchman is Yumiki Yoda Matsuo. The hember is Yumiki Yoda Matsuo.
I don't know who she is except Yoda.
Seriously, I don't know.
I know who it is.
I know who Yoda is.
He's short.
And Yoda...
Wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute.
It's funny. It's funny.
Yoda looks a little bit like him.
Yes, he does.
Just don't take the glasser off when you cut it off.
Please don't do that, please don't do that.
It would be more interesting if you had a little mustache.
Please put on a glasser, it's the glasser championship.
Matsuo.
He's the owner of a pub or something.
Yes.
He's a bit of a rock star... and a pub singer.
He's cute.
Yumiki, right?
Yes.
I was wondering who Yumiki really is.
A skinny guy.
No, I won't take it.
I really don't know who she is.
Interesting.
You're late.
I knew it.
I'd be embarrassed if it wasn't for the glasser.
It's true, it's a bit...
The first time I put on the wig...
I had to laugh, to be honest.
That's true.
But when I put on the glasser and the mustache, I couldn't laugh anymore.
Oh, my God.
You are... Oh, my God, you're...
But seriously, Yoda looks like you.
I think Yoda can keep doing this.
But he's in.
You're in.
I like this team a lot.
Everyone looks good.
Yes, they do.
They look good.
They look good... and real.
Real... what makes it real?
Real.
Yes!
It's real.
How many points did you give it?
How many points did you give me?
Five.
No, it's huge!
Five points is huge.
This is an extraordinary episode.
We haven't had a show like this for 12 years.
Yes, if a foreigner saw it...
They think Japanese TV is strange.
That's what happens when you go abroad sometimes.
Yes, it does happen.
They say, "What is this program?
Okay, let's go to the next team.
Let's go!
Here we go.
Oh, here they are.
Masaichi...
I don't get it. Who's this? I don't get it. Who's this?
Who's that?
Gnobi, right? I just figured it out. Gnobi, yes. Only Gnobi, I see now.
Do you have it?
A black body.
Who is it?
The beard comes off, doesn't it?
A dimple. Is it a dimple?
Where do you think it comes from?
I don't know who that is.
I don't know.
So, Masayuki Suzuki's team and Martin's team.
I didn't know who they were, except for the blacks.
I honestly don't know.
Kubo.
Kubo?
And Kaki?
Kaki?
Kaki.
I didn't recognize the persimmon either.
What do you think? Aren't you embarrassed by the sunglasses?
Nothing.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm telling you the truth, I'm telling you the truth.
Kaki and that stuff, too, in the sideshow, you know, they do it in a rather unashamed way.
I was too worried that I didn't have anything on my face.
What about now?
He's got a big heart now.
Ura, you're amazing.
Score points!
It was really good, wasn't it?
On a scale of one to ten.
Six.
I got a 6.
You got a hell of a score.
It was a hell of a score.
A little bit of eye.
I knew there was something pretty and fair-skinned about you.I knew she was pretty and fair-skinned.
I'm surprised the Nogizaka side allowed this.
It's true.
Yoda and tomorrow's team will be taller than the other two, so they'll be like bodyguards in the back.
Well then, let's go with the last team.
Here it comes!
I hope it doesn't come off.
Who's that?
Oh, that's great!
Oh, wow.
Thank you for watching.
It's nice.
Is this Endo?
It's good. It's good.
It's nice.
It's beautiful, beautiful.
Yo!
No, no, no, no, Stan, this is Koji Ayano's team.
I knew it. Zula's a different type, so...
No, they're all good.
It's a very good board, Mr. Ray Pon and our Zuraibeau!
And the uniforms match!
Iwamoto looks good again, doesn't he?
There are punks like him.
Like in our time.
Yes, yes!
Hayashi's dance was so sharp.
"Deng deng deng deng deng deng" part.
That part is the best.
That was great.
I knew you were doing it.
You did it!
I've already taken it in private.
Oh, really?
I taught it to him because it was just the two of us.
What do you mean, you taught him?
If he did it, I only know Wacky.
So he's done all of these? Is that all Wacky did?
No, um, I have quite a few friends.
You don't have many.
I have a lot of friends, but when I go to karaoke with my friends.
I wanted to liven things up.
I memorized it.
I see... I see...
I'd like to see your eyes.
Hayashi, you're like a cartoon delinquent.
Hayashi, you're really cool.
It shows off Hayashi's good side.
No, I'm hiding most of it.
But by doing this, you can see his good side even more.
But then again, the end is...
This is something...
No, I get it.
It's nice.
Maybe in the future you'll come as some kind of jewelry ambassador or something like that.
You know, in an eccentric outfit or something.
Okay, here's a point for you.
Four extra points.
Four points.
That means we're bringing in the Martin team.
That's what happened.
I see.
So, here are the karaoke scores with Master Shibata's points added
One day, Mr. Sakurai's team
No, we're in first place. We're out.
What do you think, Yumiki?
It's the sunglasses, isn't it?
It was the sunglasses, wasn't it?
I don't know. I don't feel happy at all.
Well, I don't think so.
When I put on the sunglasses, everyone became calm.
They're all sitting so firmly.
But there's a lot of pressure.
There is pressure.
Seriously, the next time I'm on another singing show, if I'm sitting in a huddle like this...Seriously, the next time you're on another singing show and you're sitting in a huddle with this...
Seriously, this group is so cool.
I can't believe I'm going to let you do this.
So, now that we've got that out of the way...
Mr. Himura, please.
The first game was to imitate the audience.
Yay!
I can do anything!
So, when you get a subject, do your best mimicry immediately!
It doesn't matter if it's similar or not, as long as you do it with all your might, you get 1 point!
The challenge was to do the best imitation you could.
Let's start with the Yosui Inoue team's challenge!
The judge, Mr. Himura, was also wearing sunglasses as an official judge!
Amazing!
Mr. Himura, the similarities are there, but it's whether or not you're doing it with a swinging attitude.
That's right.
If that happens, I'll get you out of here.
Yes, sir.
Tsutsui first. Tsutsui, are you okay?
Yes, I am.
What do you mean, "Yes"?
Yes, that's good.
Okay, then.
Okay.
Here we go.
Let's start miming!
Three, two, one.
Goi goi goi.
Here it comes.
You've swept it all off your feet.
You're not shy, are you?
I don't.
Yes, come on, nine. Yes, come on. Nine.
Three, two, one.
Gigyo-gyo?
Giggles?
You're not ashamed, are you?
Yes, sir.
Yes, I did it.
Three, two, one.
Wohohohohoho.
Wohohohoho.
That's good. You're swinging it.
No, I'm in all kinds of drama
Oh, oh, wow, wow, wow
Yes, I am.
Yes, you've been in a lot of dramas.
You're a gorilla.
He's got it. Well... We're done with our first win.
Naoki Hanzawa.
I'll do it even if I don't know.
Cry!
Cry! I don't have that line.
This is totally...
No, it's good. You were really swinging it.
Cry!
Double payback! I mean, normally...
Fireworks! Fireworks!
Three, two, one.
Shoo! Boom!
Oh, this is a bad one.
Oh, no!
Okay, I got a taste.
Three, two, one.
There are 100 kinds of White!
White comes in 200 colors! This towel is one of them!
Oh, my goodness, we made it through.
Last one, last lap!
Three, two, one.
Buckin' hard. Buckin' difficult.
Boom-boom
Paron, Yoo-chun.
Let's go a little further.
Did you get it right?
One more time.
Hello, YouTube. I'll introduce you today.
Are you a little shy? Are you smiling?
Robot.
What are you introducing?
It's a shame.
I turned it on the tele, didn't I?
I got a red one.
I laughed a little. Is that bad? By myself.
You went with red?
I did.
Now.
A little more, please.
Now's the time to study.
Last, last, last.
Now's the time to use your wits.
You say that?
Come on, last minute.
It's me.
What are you gonna do?
I ain't got black joints.
I got a chin.
Let's go for a walk.
What do you mean, "Let's go for a walk"?
Why do you say, "Let's go for a walk"?
What's that?
This is amazing.
This place is strong.
huh? Was Hanzawa strong?
What was Hanzawa's name again? What was Hanzawa about?
Cry!
Cry! What did he say?
Yamashita too.
Isn't the one about Mr. Himura just bad-mouthing him?
No, no, no.
What?
Let's go for a walk.
Who are you rubbing shoulders with?
I feel good.
Like a sunglass high.
You have a "sunglass high"?
I'm so expressive.
I can't help it.
I want to do more.
Want to do more?
I can go around the audience.
I feel like I'm shaking, do you want to do more?
Shibata, how's it going?
It's good.
Good.
You want to do it, don't you, Shibata?
I am.
That's not a good reaction, Shibata-san.
Tonight is for you.
This is how it's going to be, so the rest of the team has to go too.
Oh no!
Okay, let's go... Alfie Sakurai's team.
Alfie Sakurai's team.
What are you staring at?
Why did you say we're dating a cancer?
I don't know.
What are you doing?
He saw me.
I didn't do it.
What are you looking at?
I felt like he was trying to pick a fight with me.I felt like I was being sold a fight.
Please stop it.
Stop fighting!
We're going to play a game.
Well, then, let's play in order.
Now, here's an off-the-limiter mimicry!
Let's see what Alfie Sakurai's team can do!
Let's start!
Three, two, one.
Get it!
Go for more!
Gets!
Do!
Red! Red! Red!
I guess I got a little shy.
Oh no, you can't get any more red.
Fush! Go!
Fush! No!
Yeah!
Fush! Gillipshaw!
OK!
All right.
Come on, Yumiki.
Here we go.
Three, two, one.
Two points.
Good luck.
Three, two, one.
Come on, man.
It's so hard.
Speak up, speak up!
Whoo!
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
Oh, wow.
Oh, yeah.
That's good.
I got it, I got it.
Three, two, one. Three, two, one.
Ugh.
You drive.
You're driving.
Are you laughing?
I'm smiling.
Oh, no.
Oh, that way. I do most of the sounds.
Three, two, one.
Target.
Stop it, stop it, stop it, stop it.
Where's that scene?
I've never seen a buggy like that.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no...
Stop it!
What did he say before that?
Bitch!
Oh, no!
That's funny.
Three.
Two.
Ashidana.
Omai
Mr. Himura
Yes, it is.
That's not old-fashioned.
It's a bad one, Yashiro's
It's Ashida.
I'm Ashitama.
I'm wearing sunglasses today.
I'm feeling a little wild, aren't I?
It's a mixture of all kinds of things.
It's wild, right?
Three.
Three, two...
What about you, Mr. Ashida?
Oh, what's that? Oh, what's that?
Poh!
It's Mr. Egashida, isn't it?
What's that, Pooh?
Push it, push it, push it, push it
Push it!
You just did it, Mr. Egashida.
Ayaka!
I got a red one, didn't I?
How hard can it be?
What?
We are Sumijiro Kamado.
The second one.
Three.
Three
Ryuryu Mai
Go!
That was fun.
And I'll do it this way with F1.
If you go for the F1 betas, you'll hear the sound of them passing by.
I thought you were going to do that.
Like a whoosh.
I remember now.
That's a bold move.
Takeshi-san!
Takeshi's dislocated.
I get the vibe, but...
Takeshi-san talks a lot.
I don't know what to cut out
Like, "What an asshole!" or "Duncan, you son of a bitch!
You're the dumbest son of a bitch.
That was it.
Put it on me.
Don't say, "Put me in!
Mizuki Yamashita's second photo book will be released on April 23
Mizuki Yamashita's graduation concert will go on sale to the general public on the 27th.
Good evening.Good evening.
My name is Masayuki Suzuki.
I'm still in the process of putting on my beard.
I hope you're having a good time today.
I hope you had a good time today.
This is Yuna Shibata.
Please subscribe to my channel and give me a high rating!
Bye bye!